http://www.oldgoldfreepress.com/oldgoldinfo/privacy.shtml

The OldGold Purdue Sports Net:
| ADVERTISE
Celebrating 20 years on the Internet in March of 2015 !
Boiler UP!
Hammer Down!
Covering Boilermaker
Athletics since 1995!
Current Site Visitors Online: 36 visitors
OldGoldFreePress.comHOME
BASKETBALL
MENS HOOPS MAIN
RECRUITING (M)
BOILERS IN THE PROS
WOMEN HOOPS MAIN
RECRUITING (W)
SPORTS NEWS
SPORTS NEWS (FACEBOOK)
Privacy Policy
Old Gold Free Press has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Old Gold Free Press Sports Network
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.
Your IP address is also used for control purposes within the Old Gold Free Press forums.
Cookies
Our Site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. We also use cookies for automatic retreival of name and e-mail information within the Old Gold Free Press forums.
Advertisers
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Personal Information
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.
Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.
Site Statistics
Old Gold Free Press uses statistics software to analyze traffic to this web site. Unlike some tracking services this statistics software does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor, but rather only collects aggregate data.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. Old Gold Free Press is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Special Relationships
We have working arrangements / agreements with several web sites to provide content to our viewers.
These content providers, in most cases, have their own privacy policies that should be consulted before making any assumptions about their policies
Some of our working agreements are with:
ecalnow.com
zzn.com
cafepress.com
lightsoutsports.com
customawards.com
commission-junction.com
e-news.com
Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Security:
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
We also use IP addresses and domain names to restrict / block accesss to certain sections of our web site.
Contacting the Web Site:
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: Old Gold Free Press Sports Network
As news organizations move their stories to an archive, some of the links listed above may become inactive
OldGoldFreePress COLUMNISTS
OGFP_Staff
-Career Blocked Shots Rankings
Bob_Richards
-Women's Recruiting Update: Liza Clemons No. 1
Steve
-Opponent #11: University of Wisconsin
MDC -NCAA: (5 seed) Purdue 76 - (4 seed) Washington 74
Capri_Small
-Purdue 76, Western Illinois 44
Jimmy_D
- Gazing into the Crystal Bubble, Part III: SEC / Big Ten / PAC 10
Brad_Jewell
-Introducing Purdue Sports News via Facebook
Bob_Sienicki
-Nike Camp: Elena Delle Donne Interview
Bob_Sternvogel
-Nike Camp Report #1 (Sparks and Monarchs)
Guest_Columnist
-Gazing into the Crystal Bubble, Part III: The SEC/Big Ten/PAC 10
Others
-Purdue Sports Info
Current Site Visitors Online: 36 visitors
Share
OldGoldFreePress.com is organized & maintained by a group of college sports reporters with the help of Purdue sports fans everywhere. OldGoldFreePress.com is an independent and unofficial Purdue (+ Big Ten Conference/NCAA) sports news site that is not affiliated with Purdue University, the Big Ten Conference, the NCAA and/or any university athletic program.
Current Site Visitors Online: 36 visitors
Share
© OldGoldFreePress.com 1995-2014
